http://www.daretoaks.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy – Dare To Aks
ForumsLogin
Dare To Aks Talk And News About Our Differences HomeForumsBlog TopicsAll RecentAgeClassDisabilities/ChallengesGenderGeneralGeographyMatureOccupationOrientationRace/EthnicityReligionGuidelinesAboutWho We AreWhy We Do ThisMedia reactionYour reactionAwardsThe Original: yforum.comAbout DifferencesAgeismDisabilityDiversityRacismReligionSexismSexualityContact UsPrivacy PolicyUser AgreementWhy “Aks”?SpeechesBooksHome / Privacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyDareToAks.Com – Privacy PolicyThis privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally identifiable information’ (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in U.S. privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, credit card information or other details to help you with your experience.When do we collect information?We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to a newsletter, fill out a form or enter information on our site.How do we use your information?We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:To personalize user’s experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.To improve our website in order to better serve you.To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.To quickly process your transactions.To potentially send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services.How do we protect visitor information?Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.We implement security measures when a user places an order enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.Do we use ‘cookies’?Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.We use or may use cookies to:Help remember and process the items in the shopping cart.Understand and save user’s preferences for future visits, which enables us to provide you with improved services.Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third party services that track this information on our behalf.You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser’s Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.If users disable cookies in their browser:Some features may or will be disabled. It will turn off some of the features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly.Third Party DisclosureWe do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, as long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety.However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising or other uses.Third party linksOccasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.GoogleGoogle’s advertising requirements can be summed up by Google’s Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. See https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en.We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website, or may use it in the future.Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie or other cookies enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.We have implemented the following, or may in the future:Remarketing with Google AdSenseGoogle Display Network Impression ReportingDemographics and Interests ReportingWe along with third-party vendors such as Google use or may use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions, and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.Opting out: Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising initiative opt out page or permanently using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.California Online Privacy Protection ActCalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law’s reach stretches well beyond California to require a person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting personally identifiable information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals with whom it is being shared, and to comply with this policy. See more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpufAccording to CalOPPA we agree to the following:Users can visit our site anonymously.Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page, or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our website.Our Privacy Policy link includes the word ‘Privacy’, and can be easily be found on the page specified above.Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes:On our Privacy Policy PageUsers are able to change their personal information:By logging into their account.How does our site handle do not track signals?We honor do not track signals and do not track, plant cookies or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.Does our site allow third party behavioral tracking?We may allow third party behavioral tracking.COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation’s consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online.We do not specifically market to children under 13.Fair Information PracticesThe Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:We will notify users via in-site notificationWithin 1 business dayWe also agree to the individual redress principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or a government agency to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.CAN SPAM ActThe CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.We may collect your email address in order to:Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.Process orders and to send information and updates pertaining to ordersWe may also send you additional information related to your product and/or service.We may market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurredIf at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at info @ daretoaks.com.Contacting UsIf there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.DareToAks.cominfo at daretoaks.comLast Edited on 10-2-2017Share this:TweetShare on Tumblr 2016-01-08
Search for:
TRENDING TOPICSMost popular topicsTopics with no repliesUSERS’ NEW QUESTIONS skincell pro skin tag remover skincell pro amazon The best Aluminium Composite Panels Manufacturer in India The reason my personal dick is really smal? Can you guide everyone?USERS’ NEW REPLIES Marriage day: why do many lesbians dress like a man? effect of product names in other countrys effect of product names in other countrys Why did Christians vote for Donald Trump?FORUMSA Welcome to the DareToAks.com ForumsAge-relatedClassDisabilities/ChallengesGenderGeneral DiversityGeographyMatureOccupationRace/EthnicityReligionSexual Orientation @DareToAks We’re closing in on 20,000 views on FB/YouTube! Please pass along maybe @NeilYoung will see it! https://t.co/2qfKyAdSP12018/09/20 So little time, so many young minds to offend.
I’ll be at Kean University discussing https://t.co/9QWRNSPspo Wed.… https://t.co/sfut6HRRTd2018/09/17 Multiracial musicians reimagine Neil Young’s “Southern Man” as “Northern Man.” https://t.co/2qfKyAdSP12018/09/17 Just in to https://t.co/9QWRNSPspo: Deaf, blind and doing it: how does it feel? https://t.co/GPbbYApK6k2018/09/14 Wow @MoviePass. Just wow. #MoviePass disingenuousness = Movie Pass https://t.co/CTDs34Vp7e2018/08/03SOCIAL RecentPopularCommentsTags Asking THOSE PEOPLE: New books spotlight 20 years of taboo cross-cultural questions January 13, 2020 ‘Michele, Ma belle…’ OK to date her, please? September 19, 2018 Deaf, blind and doing it: how does it feel? September 14, 2018
Asking THOSE PEOPLE: New books spotlight 20 years of taboo cross-cultural questions – Dare To Aks: […] Awards […]...
‘Michele, Ma belle…’ OK to date her, please? – Dare To Aks: […] the dialogue on this post and see what others are saying here. Login t...
Deaf, blind and doing it: how does it feel? – Dare To Aks: […] Join the dialogue on this post and see what others are saying here. Lo...
hispanic Donald Trump gender sex handicapped deaf wheelchair LGBQT transgender Grammar Race Aks Military Sept. 11 Latina beauty poverty mattress arm hair style World Trade Center makeup chola girl body hair eyelinerSearch Forums Search for:
Login or RegisterSubscribeGuidelinesForumsBlog Archives Blog Archives Select Month January 2020 September 2018 July 2018 January 2018 September 2017 June 2017 April 2017 March 2017 February 2017 November 2016 October 2016 September 2016 August 2016 July 2016 June 2016 May 2016 April 2016 About usContact UsPrivacy PolicyUser Agreement
This site and all its content, ©Copyright Phillip J. Milano 1997-Beyond
